#### Contact

abhilole@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/abhishek-lole-90786a126 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

ANSYS

Microsoft Excel

Microsoft Office

# Abhishek Lole

Associate Consultant at TCS | Techno-commercial Acumen | IIOT | ERP | Salesforce CRM

Pune

## Summary

Experienced Team Lead with a demonstrated history of working in the mechanical industry, Currently serving IT companies to explore New Sales & Marketing strategies for cloud based solutions for Manufacturing, Pharma, Chemicals, FMCG. Skilled in Business Development, Business Relationship, Client Handling, Client Presentation, Finite Element Analysis (FEA), and Presentation Skills. Strong information technology professional graduated from Sinhgad Academy of Engineering.

### Experience

Tata Consultancy Services
Associate Consultant
April 2019 - Present (1 year 5 months)
Pune Area, India

\*Build and retain a world class team focused on delivering according to business objectives.

\*Ensure all data is captured, tracked and qualified leads are entered into the CRM leads management system

\*Deliver information on programs, promotions and products via phone, email, fax, etc.

Provide feedback and suggestions for program improvement on a weekly basis

\*Influence (or impact or promote) market share in a defined territory or industry vertical.

Exceeds various business objectives

- \*Develop and execute against a comprehensive account/territory plan.
- \*Create & articulate compelling value propositions
- \*Influence (or impact or promote) customer adoption.
- \*Maintain a an accurate forecast and various business reports
- \*Work with partners to extend reach & influence (or impact or promote) adoption.

\*Possess the technical ability to explain (not implement) Cloud Computing, infrastructure solutions (Server, Storage, DC Services) & Internet architectures (firewalls, load balancers, etc).

Develop case studies.

\*Develop long-term strategic relationships with key accounts.

QLB Marketing Insights, Your Strategic Sales Partner Team Lead | Business Development Manager I International Businesses

October 2018 - March 2019 (6 months)

Pune Area, India

Business Development Executive | Project Manager | Best New Joinee Award |

As a Business Development Executive I am responsible for

- -B2B Lead Generation | B2C | Developing Business Strategies | Business Acumen
- -Cold calling | Email Marketing | Building Marketing Strategies for Cloud Based Software
- -Understand the clients' business issues,
- -Operating business rules, data, and processes.
- -Interact with internal or client teams to resolve any issues.

As a Project Manager I am responsible for -

- -Handling lead Generation Campaign of Cloud Based Solution for Manufacturing Industries ( --Automotive , Pharma , Chemical , FMCG SME's ).
- -Targeting and positioning ERP solution to COO, CEO level.
- -Conducting and managing sentiment analysis, polling across FMCG, CD and SME segments.
- -Monitoring Deep interviews and surveys with SME's.

As a Market Analyst I am responsible for

- -Collecting data on consumers, competitors and market place and consolidating information into actionable items, reports and presentations.
- -Understanding business objectives and designing surveys to discover prospective customers' preferences.
- -Compiling and analyzing statistical data using modern and traditional methods to collect it.
- -Perform valid and reliable market research SWOT analysis.
- -Interpret data, formulate reports and make recommendations

<sup>\*</sup>Ensure customer satisfaction.

- -Use online market research and catalogue findings to databases
- -Provide competitive analysis on various companies' market offerings, identify market trends, pricing/business models, sales and methods of operation
- -Evaluate program methodology and key data to ensure that data on the releases are accurate and the angle of the release is correct
- -Remain fully informed on market trends, other parties researches and implement best practices
- -Working on enterprise health tech platforms targeted towards CHROS, and HR change agents.

#### ASA TECH SOLUTIONS

Senior Business Analyst June 2017 - December 2017 (7 months)

Salesforce Admin Badges -

Salesforce Platform Basics | Data Modeling |

Data Management | Lightning Experience Customization |

Salesforce Mobile App Customization | User Engagement |

Reports & Dashboards for Lightning Experience |

Business acceleration & scale-up | Customer value creation | Commercial excellence of leadership | Product development & portfolio strategy | High performing team

| Researching organisations and individuals online (especially on social media) to identify new leads and potential new markets |

Researching the needs of other companies and learning who makes decisions about purchasing

Contacting potential clients via email or phone to establish rapport and set up meetings |

| Planning and overseeing new marketing initiatives |

| Attending conferences, meetings, and industry events |

#### Team Automachen

1 year 11 months

Team Captain

February 2016 - November 2017 (1 year 10 months)

we design and manufacture gokarts for national level go karting events.

#### FEA Analyst

January 2016 - September 2016 (9 months)

pune

analysis of Automotive parts in Ansys workbench and Hypermesh

Mechanical Engineer February 2016 - February 2016 (1 month)

Pune, Maharashtra, India

Job is to design the transmission system of go kart

### Education

Sinhgad Institutes, Pune.

Bachelor of Mechanical engineering · (2014 - 2017)

Adarsh institute of Technology and Polytechnic Vita

Diploma In Mechanical Engineer, Mechanical Engineering · (2011 - 2014)